# Julian Garcia-Schroeder

Phoenix, Arizona

julian.gschroeder1999@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/julian-garcia-schroeder-81271123a

### **BUSINESS ANALYST**

Spanish and English speaking analyst with about 1 year of IT operations experience looking to break Into the business intelligence domain. With plenty of experience project managing and communicating with stakeholders and other cross-functional teams, I am ready to tackle business analysis. I have completed courses In SQL, Excel, Tableau, Power BI, and project management to make sure my transition into this scope Is a smooth one.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### NALCAP - Madrid, Spain Language Assistant

Oct 2023 -- July 2024

Working as an Auxiliar de Convercacion in Madrid, Spain. Assisted as part of a cultural exchange program being an aid for the teacher to help with English subjects, terms, vocabulary, etc. During this time I studied SQL, statistical analysis, Excel, Tableau, Power BI, and project management.

## Grand Canyon Education - Phoenix, Arizona IT Support Analyst III

Jan 2023 - Sept 2023

On-campus/onsite helpdesk role troubleshooting various different software and hardware issues for staff at GCU/GCE, either by remote access or in-person. I would: manage user accounts across several domains via Active Directory/Azure & Intune/FIM/SCCM; triage tickets via Service Desk; maintain proper asset/inventory upkeep and complemented the Warehouse team with tasks; set up workstations, maintain printers and various other vendor owned equipment; maintain relationships with vendors; regularly communicated with business-side stakeholders in various cross-functional teams; assist with events involving technology; and create process workflows for both customers and in-house training.

### DT Mobile Detailing - Phoenix, Arizona Detailer

August 2019 - Jan 2023

Polished, waxed, buffed, washed, and detailed cars of all types. Face-to-face customer service role where I would have to understand the needs of the client in order to provide the best work possible.

### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **Bachelor of Science**

Information and Computer Science - 3.46 GPA Park University - Gilbert, AZ

**Google Project Management Certification**Coursera

**Excel, SQL, Statistical Analysis Cert** Udemy

### **PORTFOLIO**

https://www.canva.com/design/DAGDVFY1cEs/qfRlS6dPJvmYbd9ikWXatg/view?
utm\_content=DAGDVFY1cEs&utm\_campaign=designshare&utm\_medium=link&utm\_source=editor